hello
welcome back to another episode of
hermitcraft
i every time i start an episode i seem
to find myself in a new and strange
predicament it looks
it looks like i've got like my phone and
i'm taking i'm taking like a vlog in a
really cramped space um well the
situation is i am literally stuck
between many many pandas probably not
what you expected look there's one there
hello and i found myself in this hole
i've i
hello
i am stuck i can't get out they're so
chunky i
can't get out i've made some panda pens
for breeding my only chance is when they
sneeze i then i then rush out so
everyone jump for joy
okay it doesn't work uh there's no other
way there's no other way i'm gonna have
to fight my way out
oh
okay so you're probably wondering why i
ended up getting stuck inside a panda
breeding center well that's because
there is a bounty on the board for five
panda heads and
yeah pandas have the lowest rate of
dropping a minecraft head i've ever seen
so i started a mass breeding program
so i can try and get it but so far it's
not gone so well jump for joy if you
love good times with scar
jump for joy if you love mumbo jumbo
oh
there's a proper panda wave okay let's
see if we have any luck they hurt they
hurt a lot come on
just one head
i'm almost convinced that they just
don't drop the minecraft heads
i am well the breeding program continues
because this doesn't look like it's
going to be very fruitful
well we'll continue the panda breeding
program but
at this point i've spent so much time on
it that i'm not sure that they even drop
minecraft heads wow scars village is
really coming along something nice
this is really cool but today the focus
is going to be once again
on trying to get the invisible mansion
this one
this one a bit more complete i want to
get the mansion here
well i want to start working on this
section or maybe the side sections
something but i definitely need to make
a bit more progress now that i have done
all the excavating that i wanted to do
because i can't i can't leave it like
this what a mess
what a mess and also i've realized look
at this the issues we're gonna have with
snow
i really don't want to have to put
string all over this base but i may have
to but just before let's run our errands
and check on the shopping district
the hms ggg has been trading and i can't
keep it stocked for long enough
i cannot seriously
every time i stock it up i'm like hey
guys stock up and then it's like yeah
empty we're also selling some some
golden carrots
we're making we're making we're just
stocks this is good this is good i think
we can upgrade again today so how much
did we make wow wow wow wow and i've
even been doing some custom orders for
people who need it xp crafted
one two three four i only build him two
diamonds he wanted a custom order and i
got him and he gave me four diamonds
what a nice guy so look at that nearly a
stack and a half of diamonds well i
think we can put that to good use and
finally upgrade the barge so this is the
investment pile that will be three
diamond blocks that will get us enough
land to build the boat we'll come back
to that a little later let's go and get
ourselves some good stock after we have
checked on the bounty board we are
currently first place with 3 300 points
and second place is false's team with 2
300. we've got quite a nice lead and
hopefully we can secure the victory on
this one
right
as i was saying let's go and get some
stock it's a bit boring but it's got to
be done
[Music]
after all of that grinding there are
some new bounties on the board you might
be a bit sick of the head game but i am
certainly not i need all the points i
can get one panda head one panda head
we need we need this i've got it i've
got
when did i pick that up
what
i almost i almost don't even want to
submit
it's so rare i didn't even realize i
must have got one when i was getting the
pandas earlier
um
that's a bit of a bind to give up
but i'm doing it i'm doing it now i'm
gonna have to grind for another one but
the new bounties i have so many i can do
i've got the cod heads i've got maybe
five different hermit heads as well
quick back to the base wait scott give
me fruit the man the man constantly has
fruit no
he's run out of fruit we have to walk we
have to go back the old-fashioned way
there's only five days left of the head
game so we've got to act quickly what
kind of wizard am i
you're
you're a harry wizard
sorry i i could i can't i can't resist a
good harry potter pun
five different hermit heads
i can do there's the impulse kill one
two three four all right quickly quickly
quickly submit these before someone else
does you have to understand me and scar
are too far into this game we have to
we've been working so hard
if we lose i don't know what i'll do
i've wasted so much time all right here
we go 20 cod heads
look at this double points is impulse
and i got a bounty on impulse right here
what
a good submission
this has been i mean i've i've spelt a
lot of these wrong
1050 1
250 points submitted okay that's enough
for the head game today i promise
i i i think we've done quite well there
and we're still first wait who the god
boy god boy and wizard chap
[Laughter]
do you really you really think i look i
do i look i look exactly like the cod
it's like it's like a bargain grid
okay right we have secured our points
even further
looking good everyone all right let's go
to the base where we are going to
continue working on our well building
our big old mansion let's go
so last episode we worked out that we
need a quite a steep staircase that goes
up to the mansion now in today's time
lapse i actually want to do two things i
want to create some towers that go
either side here and i want some towers
on the side we're not going to touch
anything around the back yet until we've
worked out everything on the front i
want this to feel a little bit more
grand than it currently is and the other
thing i want to do is work out how the
pathway is going to go up to here so i'm
thinking it runs down here it then has a
middle bit it splits into two and down
the side again there's no there's no
wrong way to build not at all just some
things look slightly better than others
in your opinion so let's crack on get
this
let's get this going
[Music]
well i am pretty happy
with how this has all come out look at
those towers
i think they look absolutely spectacular
this is getting more and more like
disney castle every single day and the
fact that there's going to be even more
build here i think this will be
phenomenal unfortunately we still have
the issue
of um
being a bit lackluster on the other half
towers are just floating uh not even
detail but you know we'll get to this in
good time now i have actually planned
out this section here but unfortunately
i did run out of resources and time yet
again so we'll have to come back to that
next episode and also i didn't actually
show you the
sheer amount of gravel
and sand i collected from that time
lapse earlier in the video check it out
look at all this i'm actually gonna
transport most of this over to the barge
right now to get this on sale three
shulker boxes of each should be enough
to get this all stocked up
oh message time
mumbo
mambo sent a message
what have we got what have we got
some kippers for you
the man sent me some fish
send me some fish
i guess i can give these to my new cats
i found some cats and i've just been uh
yeah just keep oh come on
literally the most annoying thing in the
world
they just literally straight away hop on
top of the chest and then you can't open
them
come on bro
either way let's go to the shopping
district and get this all stocked up
we've had some more sales from the
carrots and we are all stocked up on
gravel and sand i'm facing a little bit
of a dilemma with this because
i actually really love this silly design
of the barge
and i feel like
i feel like i don't really want to get
rid of it it's part of the story so i'm
wondering whether i keep this and rename
it something like green's bargain barge
and then actually take the profits and
reinvest it elsewhere for a bigger
better shop
not entirely sure let me know keep the
barge and make another shop or
get rid of the barge and make the shop
right there i mean it's a prime location
but there's just something really
charming about this barge i don't know
what it is i just really like it
so let me know what you think
and a little update on the leaderboard
we are still in first place brian brian
and carr i mean
cleo you're not even trying anymore to
ensure that we get our victory
i think it's time that me and scar
started preparing
for the last ditch effort
it all ends tomorrow let's do it i can't
give too much away because i don't
really want it being spoiled to the
other hermit i don't want anyone
stealing my idea to win the head hunt
game
good times with scar light your stuff up
but we are going to need an awful lot
again
mumbo
mumbo we play now
we play now
what is this
hey bird hope you're okay fancy a game
i'll start naughts and crosses
oh okay yeah
he's gone straight for the middle okay
there we go x and i'll even leave a
happy face for him done and we'll send
it off
enjoy mumbo
i'm pretty sure in naughts and crosses
you can win as long as you move first so
there's a there's a good chance that i'm
uh yeah i'm just gonna lose but it's i
think that's a really good idea i've got
loads of cats around here and this cat
this cat whenever i'm not looking
starts eyeing up the bird like he he
wants to go after him the cats don't eat
parrots right right they don't they're
you you you're not going to eat
professor beak right
and you keep your you keep your mitts
off him he's a precious angel
and there's another message
people do like to leave me some messages
today please accept these free samples
courtesy of impulses emerald and totem
shop please consider buying some stuff
so a bit of marketing going on home way
emeralds and a totem of undying
how amazing brilliant okay well i
actually could use these emeralds
because for our secret plan scar and i
are going to need an awful lot of bread
now i have been actually trading a lot
with these guys in order to get you can
see these stacks and stacks and stacks
of bread but if we continue it we can
end up with a really really decent
amount this is why these trading halls
are so brilliant
now ren is actually online right now so
we're going to go and head over to his
base and see if we can convince him to
give us his minecraft head
pretty sure this is his oh wait is he
here in his island
fortunately i visited red enough when
he's streaming to know where there he is
i know where his stuff is and i know
what he's after i am once again i am
once again asking for your cranial
support
will you give me your face i need it and
i can't pvp you because you didn't opt
in i burnt you at the stake once and
i've got a new way to get it out you
want to know what's in it for you huh
huh today i offer
dark oak
and a stack of golden carrots what do
you think
tasty logs come on you can sell that for
a profit that's all i got that's all i
got bro i mean i can uh
and and a
[Music]
the fish
the fish sealed the deal
all right let me set up
and we'll set up the table
oh dear
this is terrifying
are you ready for this
i'm very terrified
but i'm ready
well we've we've burned the witch and
now it's time to uh yeah come up with
new and inventive ways all right i need
you to stand right here right up against
that uh trap door
okay
yeah hopefully this works there we go
right now don't move yet i'm gonna need
you
i'm gonna need you to move
very slowly forward okay and then
backwards all right you're ready all
right three
two
one
okay
good
good stuff
do you want me to leave this here or you
want me to take this with me um please
take it with i don't think i'll be able
to sleep tonight thanks queen
all right thank you again for your
cranial support i hope you enjoy that
was it the fish that sealed the deal on
that one yeah i gotta have the fish i've
got a very hungry cat back on the island
so yeah thanks
thank you very much my dude now that
that's out of the way and i've done all
i can for today on the build
i'm very very happy with how this is
going now as for the lighting it's
actually a really difficult build to
light now i have been using these
lanterns but i'm hoping when 1.16 comes
around i can change these lanterns into
the blue ones and it will all match the
palette of what i'm going for in fact i
have built this entire mansion with 1.16
blocks in mind so in the future i will
be able to make it all match together
and it will be even more glorious than
it is now you wait you wait you'll see
how far ahead i've been planning this
build
but now
it is time for me to start preparing for
the secret win hello
hi hi how are you i'm good what's your
um plan here for your village well at
one time or another we'll have villagers
galore here running around masons giving
us courts and things but right now it's
a bit of a shiny town i'll admit that
okay so this doesn't actually look like
this would be a suitable location for
our plan we need a we need a name for
our plan
because the audience don't know what it
is so don't don't spill the beans just
yet but then
i've just been referring it to as like
our final push or the the last uh thing
like i haven't i haven't got a name i
need it i need the last laugh the last
laugh no no no
needs
like like operation aqua thunder but i
believe that's taken wait wait wait wait
wait wait it's actually operation i'll
go thunder my voice kind of crack but
that's okay
i still don't know what that is so if
you got operation aqua thunder what
would be the opposite of that operation
fire lightning fire nailed it named it
is it got like if if it's operation
is it operation fire lightning
yes you nailed it i like it got it you
get that operation aqua thunder
operation lightning thunder wait no i
goofed it up my bad
uh it doesn't look like we got a place
for it unless uh
unless we use this space here no no no
no i got plans for this this will be
this will be a farm a glorious farm
there'll be bees in everything i have
this perfect place over here it's super
out of the way it's super safe um this
is a giant beautiful barn yeah go inside
there take it take it take a stroll
i'm not
i'm not going in there
here come on just just try it like you
know come on
scarf what have you created
i flew in here earlier and it was no bad
mistake there wasn't anything
i can't fly oh gee my god
[Music]
why are you hovering there's something
wrong let me
go
no
things went so wrong the people that saw
my side could see the rockets being
consumed but i just didn't go anywhere
dude you were floating in the air like a
bee i don't know what happened
that was terrifying
no i'm not going in there scar
oh it's fine now that's fine
look at this look at this it's perfectly
fine now look at the size in the room
look at this we need to get some
refreshments we get some cake oh my gosh
could you even imagine this would have
been perfect i think it's still not
going to be big enough for operation
fire lightning so
we may need to like clear out
as much as i'm sick of clearing out
jungle we may need to clear out some
more jungle
you've got it you got an arrow like in
in your ear
that's a rough one so shall we clear out
a space for operation fire lightning
just temporarily of course
operation by a lightning
fire lightning
since we can't use scars village and
actually it would be way longer to clear
out and flatten any of this jungle it
takes hours honestly it looks like a
simple task it's not
what we're going to do is we're going to
use an area i've already previously
cleared out over here
and i'm just going to chop down all of
these trees and we'll use this because
this is kind of already my temporary
tree farm that it doesn't look very
pretty and operation fire lightning is
also not going to be very pretty so i
think we'll just use this i mean it's
still going to take me a while to chop
down all these trees but it's definitely
going to be faster than the jungle all
right this is looking a lot clearer now
and i got a lot of resources from it
this box here is all operation fire
lightning so now i need to create a
space
where we can begin but i'm afraid
that is all we're gonna have time for
today
we've got an awful lot of work to do me
and scar
and we better get started because this
is gonna be
hours and hours of work to secure our
win
for the head game
so i will see you
in the next episode of hermitcraft thank
you very much for watching and good bye
you